Please download the virtual model from the Femalemaster V2 file editor.
Use the virtual model tool in the 3D tool bar to draw a line on the virtual model.
Press the Ctrl key to add a curve point.
When the line on the virtual model is completely closed, press the Enter key to remove the flat version.
Delete excess curve points and adjust the curve to make the line smoother.
Press Ctrl D to align the flat version with the seam line, and then Shift F to show the arrangement point.
Arrange the model around the virtual model.
We can use the edit line virtual model tool to delete the line on the virtual model.
Extend the flat version to the body of the virtual model.
After selecting the flat version, you can shrink the flat version.
Move around, rotate, and so on.
Adjust the curve of the plate according to the image of the virtual model
Use the rectangle tool to create the back plate
Adjust the width of the plate by moving the outside of the plate and the point of the straight line
Control D to align the plate with the sewing line
When moving the line or the point of the straight line, right-click, you can enter the number of movement in the spring
Use the edit curve tool to adjust the curve of the plate
The length of the front and back plate is measured to ensure that the length is unified
Shift F shows the arrangement of the plate
You can adjust the position of the plate cover after selecting the plate you have arranged
You can use the vertical début tool to sew the plates together
You can adjust the position of the plate with the tolerated evident solution tool
Use the diagonal sewing tool to sew the plates together
After sewing you can move up or down the slice to attach the Juneziech paper pattern keyhole
Select the top point on the outside line of the double-chip board with the same tool for the whole line, so that the board can be fixed to avoid falling.
After measuring the length of the seam line that the shoulder strap needs to be sewn, we can use the shoulder strap of the rectangular tool to draw the shoulder strap.
Ctrl D to align the board with the seam line.
Shift F to display the arrangement points around the virtual model and arrange the board.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the board together.
To ensure that the direction of the seam line is consistent in the 3D window, we can select the free sewing tool in the 3D window for sewing.
The sewing tool selected in the 3D window can be used in the 2D and 3D windows at the same time.
Press the W key and click on the 3D window to add a pin.
For too small boards, the number of grid spaces will be relatively small.
Therefore, by reducing the number of grid spaces with the example tool, it can also make the board more detailed and smoother.
In order to be able to separate the seam lines of the symmetrical boards, we need to re-set the link relationship for the board.
Set the current symmetrical board board.
Change the seam line and seam line to symmetrical boards.
We can still adjust the board to match, such as adding internal lines.
But the seam line is not symmetrical.
Press the W key and click on the pin again.
You can delete the pin or Ctrl W to delete all pins.
By installing hangarこん Mskew, the line map of the Baukstra is very much thinner.
This literally這
кв
We can notice that there is a gap between the smart board and the virtual model,
we can set the surface of the virtual model as 0
The previous version is more suitable for virtual models.
You can use the fixed needle tool to fix the strap.
After selecting the previous version, use 100% elasticity to maintain the length of the original line.
Use the edit curve point tool to adjust the curve.
You can select the points of the inner line and align one end separately to the outer line of the version.
Since the strap is too short, the front and back panels are stretched, so we need to lengthen the strap.
Use the edit curve point tool to move the curve point.
We can apply a new fabric to the strap.
We can use trim foot grain leather,
and increase friction and inner damping.
In order to prevent the strap from being stretched or lowered,
it is advisable to maintain the shape of the original version so that it can be adjusted well and it is not easy to slip and fall.
There are many wrinkles on the back panel, we can narrow the panel a little.
We can use trim foot grain leather,
and adjust the position and size of the strap.
We can adjust the position and size of the strap.
To remove the wrinkles on the panel, we can also add a strap on the back panel.
Adjust the position and size of the strap.
Use the trim line tool to trim the hand.
Copy the front panel and then reset the 3D arrangement position.
Next, make the river side.
Choose the line and use the panel to expand the outer line.
If you change the side angle to Extend and select the inner line,
it will expand along the side of the curve and at the same time create the inner line in the original position.
Select and cut off the inner line, and delete the excess panels and curve points at the same time.
You can use the trim line tool to adjust the curve.
The width from the top to the bottom of the river side should be gradually increased.
Delete the curve and select the elastic.
The river side should be wider than the front and back panels, so that there will be wrinkles.
Use the trim line tool or the free trim tool to trim the panels.
To avoid the simulation being unstable, we need to freeze the panels of the skirt.
Use the side to add the side of the river side to the seam line.
Use the side to do the symmetry.
To adjust the tip of the river side to the whole list, hold down the Floral fork key to the right, and move the попol into the child.
ä
To bring the skirt to shorts, we can move the skirt to shorts, and then press sec.
We can reverse-activate the left panel, Shift-Q to hide them.
Use the free sewing tool to sew the river side and the skirt together.
Shift-C to display the hidden panels.
The cold-wet panel is selected and the layer is set to 1.
After setting the layer, it will automatically identify which panel is on the outside and which is on the inside.
After activating, slice the panel.
In order to prevent the panel from sliding down, we can add a fixing pin to fix the skirt.
After the simulation is completed, all layers are set back to 0,
to avoid unnecessary conflicts with other panels in the subsequent simulation process.
After sewing the back of the river side,
use the square tool to make the belt.
Shift-F to display the arrangement points and arrangement panels.
In the property editor, we can adjust the arrangement position of the panel.
Cold-free version
For belt application 1 layer, because the belt should be on the outer layer of the skirt
We can use the selection grid tool to select the position of the insertion
Select the grid tool
In the 3D window, use the positioning ball to drag the insertion part out
After the simulation is stable, the layer will be reset
Before the simulation, I will replace the belt fabric with TrimFool Green Leather
Make it easy to stretch and deform
Reduce the tail to green
The belt will be tightened by 50%
Please insert a bag from the Hardware and Trims Greater Than Ribbon file
Click the slide icon in the upper right corner to adjust the size of the component
Please note that each component has a corresponding weight
Therefore, we need to adjust the weight of the component in the attribute editor
Reduce the particle diameter to get more detailed fold details
If you want to remove the fold after the plate is cut out, you can use the selection tool
To set the
The